Prophecy Time
You married through media - images.
That is your first attempt - somebody you have not seen physically.
Yes, it's true, Man of God.
Just like on the internet.
It is true, Man of God, very true.
Do you want me to talk to you?
Yes.
Someone you were not seeing - through internet, through chat.
You chatted and you decided to marry the person.
It' is true, Man of God, it is true.
This is the beginning of where your life was destroyed.
Please deliver me, Man of God.
You did not see - you just chatted and didn't even know the face
whether they may send you a wrong face and you decided to marry the person.
That is how the marriage was established.
It is true, Man of God; please deliver me, Man of God.
Please deliver me.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
People of God - Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Samahar Daniel.
I came from France.
I am originally Ethiopian.
What the man of God said last week is very true.
I was actually married through the internet when I was fifteen years old.
That is something that I have never ever shared in my life.
When I came here on Sunday, I was just sitting over there.
The man of God came to me as you saw and prophesied that straight to me.
I was really shocked and surprised
and very thankful to God that He has done this for me
because I was very hopeless.
When I got married to that internet relationship -
as I told you I was fifteen years old...
After that, in the relationship that I had on the internet...
When I even used to date people or go out with some guys, I was never satisfied.
I mean the only thing that could satisfy me was having a relationship with an unknown person
that I had never seen in my entire life.
This problem led me to smoking, I used to go out and drink
when I was only fifteen and a half years old.
Every day someone around me would say, "When are you going to stop smoking?
When are you going to stop drinking?"
I used to take ecstasy, smoking cigarettes and 'weed' - 'weed' was every single day.
Each and every year, it got worse, worse and worse.
My mum sent me here for this issue last week.
When I came here I was very hopeless because whenever I used to go to church,
I used to tell the junior pastors to deliver me of my problems.
The next day I got to the church,
the pastor would come to me and prophesy everything I had told the junior pastors.
I was like, "No. God doesn't exist. It's not true, it cannot be true.
If I told someone what I was going through and he went to tell it to another person,
where was the proof that God is alive or works miracles.
When I came to the The SCOAN last week and sat over there,
I said to myself, "Ok, now we are going to see".
But I really had hope that my life would change.
I was not a believer but I would still be like, "Please, Jesus, if you are alive, please help me.
I am struggling and I am tired of it".
Because my life depended on the things I took.
I fought with my parents; with my mum.
I got very aggressive, uncontrollable.
My breakfast was cigarettes and coffee.
That was the only thing that could calm my soul.
If I didn't get that, if I didn't smoke,
I would be very mad, so aggressive and very impolite.
Even on Sunday, when I was sitting over there,
every single minute I wanted to go out and smoke.
I was actually smoking. I smoked four cigarettes before coming to church.
Even when I was here, I was fighting with the ushers to let me go out and smoke.
That I didn't feel good, please.
When the Man of God came and prophecied to me,
I said to myself, "Thank God! There is actually a true man of God in this world.
Not everyone is fooling people".
I was very happy; it was like a dream come through.
Immediately after that, people of God - I don't smoke anymore.
Miss Samahar Daniel - Prophecy Testimony
That is not enough for Jesus Christ.
Put your hands together beautifully for the miracle working God!
Miss Samahar Daniel - Prophecy Testimony
My parents used to take me to church but I never believed.
But my last experience really killed me.
I told myself that if God really existed, He would do something.
I would tell Him, "Why don't you do something? Please do something if you are here".
I came to The SCOAN with a lot of struggles.
My mum who pushed me to come here - there was even a time she was against it.
This was really meant to be. God really wanted to deliver me using the man of God.
Okay, now can you tell us what happened here that made you believe that God exists?
The prophesy was true because this was something I had never ever shared in my entire life.
This was the source of my problems.
This was the reason why I became who I was in the past.
And you didn't discuss this with anyone before coming here?
No! I had never told anyone.
Even for me - this was something that I had forgotten.
When the man of God said it, immediately I was like, "Ah! Yes! It was true!"
Whilst sitting on the seat, I was thinking about it.
In the night, I was thinking about it.
I had this flashback.
I remembered everything.
I started recollecting things.
God was showing me, "You see when I did this?"
Everything was so clear after that and so visible in my life.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
Miss Samahar Daniel - Prophecy Testimony
Now, after having received a prophecy, that made you to believe that Jesus Christ exists -
the issue that you had never discussed with anyone -
what is your belief now about the existence of Jesus?
I had never found happiness in my entire life.
Wherever I went, whatever I did, I wasn't happy.
I used to go out, smoke, do every bad stuff.
But I had never been happy in my entire life.
And yes, I do believe now that God is really here and that He watches over us and protects us.
Because I have been through a lot of things, no matter how young I was.
I used to go out, drink and find myself with an unknown man.
And then I was like, "Samahar, why did you do that? What happened?"
And this was even unexplainable to myself.
I couldn't even explain it to myself.
So yes, God has protected me and my spiritual life since then has changed
because I would never stay five minutes in a church.
No matter where my mum took me, pastors coming to our home praying for me,
I would just go out to smoke my cigarettes and argue with everyone.
For the first time in my life, I attended a whole long service -
from the morning till the night!
And I pray and read the Bible.
I thank God!
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle working God!
Miss Samahar Daniel - Prophecy Testimony
Now once again, because of how wonderful your testimony is,
and your testimony will go a long way to affect the youths all over the world positively...
Could you once again tell us, when you were addicted to this smoking and drinking,
how severe was it? How did it affect your entire life?
Could you tell us once again?
I think maybe people who have had an addiction before would understand what I'm exactly saying.
Because even not to eat breakfast is really hard.
When I got up in the morning, the only thing that I wanted to do
was just to light a cigarette and have a coffee.
Once I even burnt my hair just trying to light a cigarette.
That was the only thing I wanted upon getting up.
When my parents were around, I couldn't smoke and I had to pretend that I was not a smoker.
Then, I would start a fight - I would become aggressive and find a reason to go out and smoke.
I could have never ever stopped.
I actually thought I would end up smoking.
Really, I would end up smoking.
Everyone in my family found out that I used to smoke 'weed' and cigarettes.
If it hadn't been for God, I would have never ever got out of the situation; that's for sure.
Miss Samahar Daniel - Prophecy Testimony
To God be the glory!
Can you just tell us how this relationship you had on the internet affected your life,
in confirmation of the prophecy given by the man of God,
of which you said that you had never discussed it with anyone
and you were so shocked hearing that from the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, for the first time last Sunday.
Can you tell us how this relationship affected your life as a young lady.
It affected me in the sense that I was never happy.
I was never happy with any relationship I had.
I preferred to have a person I had never met - through images only.
That gave me satisfaction.
The untouchable made me happy,
whilst I could have had someone I knew and went through life together.
But no - the unknown would make me happier.
It affected me in the sense that I was always unfaithful to the person I was with.
We thank God Almighty for your life.
After the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, gave you that message of prophecy
and you were delivered, what are the changes that have taken place in your life,
compared to your past life?
When I came here, I came on my own.
So I was staying in a hotel.
In my hotel room, I had two packets of cigarettes and one lighter.
While I was coming to The SCOAN to stay here, I left everything that I had.
And I was even surprised that I had somehow left everything in the truck.
It is incredible.
I was the type of person who would steal lighters from people. Believe me.
If a thrown-away packet of cigarettes was on the floor, I would check if there were cigarettes in it.
I would have never thought that I would leave forty cigarettes behind.
And I am still not smoking.
I will never smoke again. I thank God.
You mean the urge to smoke and drink is completely gone after the deliverance?
Gone - 100%.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ for that!
Miss Samahar Daniel - Prophecy Testimony
Finally, as a young lady who has experienced a lot in the world,
before Jesus Christ rescued you from the shackles of satan,
what word of advice do you have for people around the world,
especially for the youth who are already into such a trap?
What do you advise them to do?
My advice would be to come to Jesus Christ
because you can never come out of this situation on your own.
I tried everything to stop; I was even in rehab back in France.
This is something that human beings cannot heal.
It is only through God. So please come to Jesus.
He has the solution for everything.
Indeed our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ is the solution to all fundamental issues of life.
Having experienced that the Lord is good,
we beseech you to continue your relationship with the Lord Jesus Christ
and we pray that as you continue your relationship with the Lord Jesus Christ,
always have it at the back of your mind that
better is not good enough, the best is yet to come.
Let us clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
Miss Samahar Daniel - Prophecy Testimony